

ABOUT ME

With a comprehensive background in both medicine and information technology, I bring a wealth of expertise to the field of Radiology. My experience is anchored in the nuanced interpretation of advanced imaging modalities, including MRI and CT scans, reflecting a commitment to precision diagnostics. Additionally, my exploration of artificial intelligence applications within Radiology underscores a forwardthinking approach, aimed at leveraging technology to optimize patient care and diagnostic accuracy.

SKILLS

IMAGING INTERPRETATION (ULTRASOUNDS, X-RAYS, CT SCANS, MRIS, ...)

DIAGNOSIS AND TREATMENT OF DISEASES

EQUIPMENT OPERATION

RESEARCH

DATA ANALYSIS

CODING (C++, PYTHON, R, ...)

COMMUNICATION

TEAMWORK

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

HOBBIES

READING BOOKS, RUNNING, PLAYING FOOTBALL

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

2ND PRIZE WINNER OF A NATIONAL CONTEST: INFORMATICS FOR YOUNG PEOPLE

Ha Noi / DEC 2014

JOINING SEMINAR FOR INTERVENTIONAL RADIOLOGY IN ASIA-PACIFIC (SIRAP) 2023 Tokyo, Japan / OCT 2023

THONG VO NGOC HUY

RADIOLOGIS

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

84911684096

vhthong.ntcdha20@ump.edu.vn

WORK EXPERIENCE

HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER

Ho Chi Minh Nov 2020 - Oct 2021

GIA DINH PEOPLE'S HOSPITAL

Ho Chi Minh Nov 2021 - Oct 2022

CHO RAY HOSPITAL

Ho Chi Minh Nov 2022 - Oct 2023

Radiology Practice

Specialized in Diagnostic Imaging: Demonstrated proficiency across key modalities including X-ray, Ultrasound, CT, and MRI.

Radiology Practice

Specialized in Diagnostic Imaging: Demonstrated proficiency across key modalities including X-ray, Ultrasound, CT, and MRI.

Radiology Practice

Skillfully executed diverse Interventional Radiology Procedures with a steadfast commitment to precision and patient safety.

EDUCATION

LONG AN HIGH SCHOOL FOR THE GIFTED

Long An 2014

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY AT HO CHI MINH CITY

Ho Chi Minh 2020

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY AT HO CHI MINH CITY

Ho Chi Minh 2023

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY AT HO CHI MINH CITY Ho Chi Minh

Information Technology Gifted Program

Graduated from Information Technology Gifted Program (Sep 2011 – Aug 2014) with an Excellent classification.

Earned Doctor of Medicine with a Good classification (Sep 2014 - Aug 2020).

Radiology Residency Program

Radiology Residency Program (Nov 2020 – Oct 2023) - Graduated with Very Good classification.

Master of Science in Radiology

Nov 2021 – Oct 2023, graduated with Excellent classification. Thesis: "Correlation between Apparent Diffusion Coefficient Value on Diffusion-Weighted Imaging and Prostate Specific Antigen with Gleason Score in Prostate Cancer."

Supervisors: Ass. Prof. Hoa Pham Ngoc; Hung Pham Thai, PhD. This study investigated the correlation between ADC, PSA and GS; as well as the performance of each metric and their combination in predicting prostate cancer malignancy.

COURSES

2023

STANDFORD UNIVERSITY

Feb 2017 - Apr 2017

DEEPLEARNING.AIMar 2019 - Jun 2019

DATACAMP Jun 2021 - Nov 2021 Machine Learning

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

Data Analyst with R

PUBLICATIONS

VIETNAMESE JOURNAL OF RADIOLOGY AND NUCLEAR MEDICINE Jan 2024

EUROPEAN CONGRESS OF RADIOLOGY 2024 POSTERS

Feb 2024

Integrated Malignancy Assessment of Prostate Cancer Using

Role of artificial intelligence in posteroanterior chest X-ray

interpretation: Preliminary initial results at Cho Ray Hospital

 Integrated Malignancy Assessment of Prostate Cancer Using Apparent Diffusion Coefficient on Diffusion-Weighted Imaging and Prostate-Specific Antigen